Leo F. Solt papers, 1643-1996 C154
Indiana University Archives
- Correspondence, 1941-1994, undated (Box 9)
  - Jezierski, John V., 1969 (Box 11)
  - Johnson, Ava L., 1945 (Box 11)
  - K, 1970-1973 (Box 11)
  - Kascht, Dr. Robert L., 1990 (Box 11)
  - Kearney, Hugh, 1967 (Box 11)
  - Knust, Richard, 1973 (Box 11)
  - Koren, Annette, 1973-1977 (Box 11)
  - Krekic, Barisa, 1972-1973 (Box 11)
  - Kruze, Uldis (Box 11)
    - 1975-1977 (Box 11)
    - 1976 (Box 11)
  - L, 1969-1973 (Box 11)
  - Lankford, Nelson, 1972-1975 (Box 11)
  - Larason, Mike, 1972-1976 (Box 11)
  - Lence, Ross (Box 11)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 11)
    - 1973 (Box 11)
  - Letters of Recommendation (Box 11)
    - 1968-1989 (Box 11)
    - 1975-1978 (Box 11)
  - Lippincott Publishers, 1965-1971 (Box 11)
  - Liu, Tai (Box 11)
    - 1969-1977 (Box 11)
    - 1982-1989 (Box 11)
  - Lovell Professorship, University of Southern California (USC), 1969-1970 (Box 11)
  - Lowry, David, 1975-1978 (Box 11)
  - Lucas, Paul (Box 11)
    - 1976 (Box 11)
    - Undated (Box 11)
  - Ludlow, Dorothy (Box 11)
    - 1972-1987 (Box 11)
    - 1974 (Box 11)
  - Lynn, Robert, 1988-1989 (Box 11)
  - Malmgreen, Gail, 1974-1975 (Box 11)
  - Malmgreen, Gail and Robert Constantine, 1980-1984 (Box 11)
  - Martinelli, Jon, 1973 (Box 11)
  - Mc, 1972 (Box 11)
  - McIntosh, Douglas M., 1972 (Box 11)
  - McMains, Howard, 1970-1976 (Box 11)
  - Mehlinger, Howard, 1969-1974 (Box 11)
  - Metz, William D., 1972 (Box 11)
  - Mitzel, John F., undated (Box 11)
  - Nagy, Peter, 1973 (Box 11)
  - Neninger, Bill and Betty, 1953 (Box 11)
  - Newberry Library (Box 11)
    - 1972 (Box 11)
    - 1987-1988 (Box 11)
  - Newhouse, Rick, 1973-1976 (Box 11)
  - Nicol, Donald, 1982-1984 (Box 11)
  - Northington, Jan, 1973 (Box 11)
  - Nugent, 1970-1972 (Box 11)
  - O, 1972-1974 (Box 11)
  - Opper, Edward, 1971-1974 (Box 11)
  - Oxford University Press (Box 11)
    - 1971-1988 (Box 11)
    - 1985-1989 (Box 11)
  - P, 1970-1974 (Box 11)
  - Pace, David, 1972-1973 (Box 11)
  - Parrott, Dan, 1969-1975 (Box 11)
  - Peters, Robert, 1952-1954 (Box 11)
  - Pitchell, Cathy, 1973 (Box 11)
  - Q, 1970-1973 (Box 11)
  - Quanungo, Bhupen, 1959 (Box 11)
  - R, 1970-1974 (Box 11)
  - Royster, David, 1970-1972 (Box 11)
  - Russell, Isa Jayne, 1972-1973 (Box 11)
  - S, 1968-1974 (Box 11)
  - Sage, Leland (Box 11)
    - 1953 (Box 11)
    - 1982 (Box 11)
    - 1988 (Box 11)
  - Salzarulo, Joanna, 1972 (Box 11)
  - Samuels, Stewart, 1972 (Box 11)
  - Sehr, Tim, 1974-1976 (Box 11)
  - Silver, Steven, 1987-1988 (Box 11)
  - Solt, Mr. and Mrs. Harry E. (Box 11)
    - 1941 (Box 11)
    - 1943 (Box 11)
    - 1944, (2 folders) (Box 11)
    - 1945 (Box 11)
    - 1946 (Box 11)
    - 1955 (Box 11)
  - Stiller, Ludwig Francis, 1972-1973 (Box 11)
  - Strom, Deanna Sue, 1973 (Box 11)
  - Student Recommendations, 1971-1972 (Box 11)
  - T, 1971-1973 (Box 11)
  - Tam, Lana, 1974 (Box 11)
  - Thompson, William Charles, 1972 (Box 11)
  - Tysl, Gloria, 1970-1976 (Box 11)
  - U, 1969-1973 (Box 11)
  - Ugland, Richard, 1974 (Box 11)
  - University of California, Davis, 1961 (Box 11)
  - University of Massachusetts Alumni, 1970-1971 (Box 11)
  - Uslan, Michael, 1972 (Box 11)
  - V, 1974 (Box 11)
  - Vassar, Rena (Box 11)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 11)
    - 1972 (Box 11)
  - Vaughan, Steve, 1974-1975 (Box 11)
  - Voight, Barbara, 1974 (Box 11)
  - W, 1969-1974 (Box 11)
  - Weinland, Helen, 1972-1973 (Box 11)
  - Wiegenstein, Jane, 1974-1978 (Box 11)
  - Wilke, Eckhardt, 1974-1975 (Box 11)
  - Workman, Katie, 1987-1989 (Box 11)
  - XYZ, 1972-1973 (Box 11)
  - Yeung, Susanna Lin-Fuj, 1972-1973 (Box 11)
  - Zaffarano, 1988 (Box 11)
  - Zaller, Robert, 1985-1986 (Box 11)
  - Zellar, Eugene D., 1989 (Box 11)
  - Zisla, Paul, undated (Box 11)
  - Zoller, Karen, 1973 (Box 11)
- Subject files, 1643-1995, undated; 1944-1995 (Box 11)
  - Age of Buckingham, undated (Box 11)
  - Age of Philip II, undated (Box 11)
  - Age of Unrest, undated (Box 11)
  - Agreement between Earls of Chester and Leicester, undated (Box 11)
  - American Historical Association (AHA) (Box 11)
    - General (Box 11)
      - 1972-1973, (2 folders) (Box 11)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 11)
      - 1974-1976 (Box 11)
      - 1975 (Box 11)
    - American Historical Review (AHR) (Box 11)
      - General, 1975 (Box 11)
      - Correspondence, 1975 (Box 11)
      - Ransel, David, Editor Evaluation, 1975-1989 (Box 11)
      - Search and Screen Committee for Editor, 1984-1985 (Box 11)
    - Annual Meeting, >, 1980 (Box 11)
    - Committee on Teaching, 1972-1973 (Box 11)
    - Council, 1974-1975 (Box 12)
    - Council Agenda (Box 12)
      - 26-30 December 1974 (Box 12)
      - 25-26 April 1975 (Box 12)
      - 28 September 1975 (Box 12)
      - 27 December 1975, (2 folders) (Box 12)
    - Council Meeting (Box 12)
      - 12 August 1975 (Box 12)
      - 28 September 1975 (Box 12)
    - Feature Films Project, 1957-1972 (Box 12)
    - Film Conference, 1967 (Box 12)
    - Film Initiatives and related, 1970-1975 (Box 12)
    - History Education Project (HEP) (Box 12)
      - 1970-1971, (2 folders) (Box 12)
      - 1970-1975 (Box 12)
    - Meeting, December 1973 (Box 12)
    - Papers, 1975-1976 (Box 12)
    - Placement, undated, 1976-1977 (Box 12)
    - Program, San Francisco, 1978 (Box 12)
    - Program Sessions, 1973 (Box 12)
    - Project in Teacher Education, Eugene Asher, 1969-1970 (Box 12)
    - Relocation, 1975 (Box 12)
    - Television and Films (Box 13)
      - 1971 (Box 13)
      - 1972-1974 (Box 13)
    - Toronto, 1967 (Box 13)
    - Vice President for Research, 1974 (Box 13)
    - Washington, 1969 (Box 13)
  - American History, Journal of, 1964-1966 (Box 13)
  - American Philosophical Society, 1957-1958 (Box 13)
  - American Revolution, undated (Box 13)
  - American Society for Church History (Box 13)
    - 1957-1991 (Box 13)
    - 1982-1985 (Box 13)
    - American Society for Reformation Research, 1958-1963 (Box 13)
    - Ancient Israel, undated (Box 13)
    - Areopagitica, undated (Box 13)
    - Association of American Publishers (AAP), Publisher – Faculty Relations Cape Cod Trip, 1976 (Box 13)
    - Association of American University Professors (AAUP), 1956-1971 (Box 13)
    - Athenian Freedom--Myth or Fact?, undated (Box 13)
    - Bacon, undated (Box 13)
    - Bibliography – Sect Development, undated (Box 13)
    - Bloomington Faculty Council (BFC) (Box 13)
      - General (Box 13)
        - 1971-1973 (Box 13)
        - 1973 (Box 13)
        - 1974 (Box 13)
      - Circular, 1972-1973 (Box 13)
      - Minutes, 1972-1973 (Box 13)
      - Student Affairs Committee, 1974 (Box 13)
    - Britain, 1950-1970 (Box 13)
    - Britain and World Power, 1954 (Box 13)
    - Britain Between the Wars, undated (Box 13)
    - Britain Comparison, undated (Box 13)
    - British Government Today, 1957 (Box 13)
    - British History, undated (Box 13)
    - British Information Services Reference Division, 1948-1955 (Box 13)
    - British Socialism, 1952-1961 (Box 13)
    - British Studies Intelligencer, 1972 (Box 13)
    - British Summer Articles, undated (Box 13)
    - Business History, 1972 (Box 13)
    - Byzantine Empire, undated (Box 13)
    - Cabinet System in 18th Century Politics, undated (Box 13)
    - Calvinism and Zwinglianism, undated (Box 13)
    - Carolingians, undated (Box 13)
    - Celts, undated (Box 13)
    - A Chairman's Notebook, Cartoons, undated (Box 13)
    - Challenge of Napoleon, undated (Box 13)
    - Charles II, undated (Box 13)
    - Charles V, undated (Box 13)
    - Chartism and Free Trade, 1967 (Box 13)
    - Church History, 1973 (Box 13)
    - John Churchill, undated (Box 13)
    - Civil War and the Execution of Charles, undated (Box 13)
    - Classical Economists, undated (Box 13)
    - Colonial Papers, undated (Box 13)
    - Colyton--Demography, undated (Box 13)
    - Commerce and Trade, 1947 (Box 13)
    - Commercial Revolution, undated (Box 13)
    - Common Debates, 1628 (Box 13)
      - 1977 (Box 13)
      - 1978 (Box 13)
    - Commonwealth and Protectorate, 1982-1989 (Box 13)
    - Communism, undated (Box 13)
    - Comparative Studies in Society and History, 1958 (Box 13)
    - Conference on British Studies, 1959-1974 (Box 13)
    - Congress of Vienna, 1954 (Box 13)
    - Council of Trent, undated (Box 13)
    - Crisis of 1789, undated (Box 13)
    - Critique of Liberalism, undated (Box 13)
    - Cromwell, 1970-1972 (Box 13)
    - Crusades, undated (Box 13)
    - Darwinism, undated; (2 folders) (Box 13)
    - Debs Foundation, 1973-1975 (Box 13)
    - Decade of Revolution, undated (Box 13)
    - Decisive Moments in History Script, 1959 (Box 13)
    - Decline of Papacy, undated (Box 13)
    - Disraeli and Gladstone, undated (Box 13)
    - Dissertations, undated (Box 13)
    - Dissolution of the Monasteries, undated; (2 folders) (Box 13)
    - Divine Right of Monarchy (James), undated (Box 13)
    - Documentary and Television Films, 1973-1976 (Box 14)
    - Domesday Book, undated (Box 14)
    - Domestic Affairs Between the Wars, undated (Box 14)
    - Dorsey Press, 1965-1971 (Box 14)
    - Early Christianity, undated (Box 14)
    - Early Greek History, undated (Box 14)
    - Early Roman Britain, undated (Box 14)
    - Early Russia, undated (Box 14)
    - East India Co., undated (Box 14)
    - Eastern Powers (Russia, Prussia, and Austria), undated (Box 14)
    - Ecclesiastical History Society, 1973-1974 (Box 14)
    - Economic and Social Consequences of the Dissolution, undated (Box 14)
    - Edinburgh Post Session Abroad, 1972 (Box 14)
    - Edward VI, undated (Box 14)
    - Edward VI and Mary, undated (Box 14)
    - Elizabeth and Catholics (Mary Queen of Scots), undated (Box 14)
    - Elizabethan Compromise, undated (Box 14)
    - Elizabethan Puritanism, undated (Box 14)
    - Enclosure and the First Planned Economy, undated (Box 14)
    - End of 100 Years War and War of the Roses, undated (Box 14)
    - England 1066-1485, undated (Box 14)
    - English Colonies in America, undated (Box 14)
    - English History Colloquium, 1972 (Box 14)
    - English History Search (Informal), 1970-1971 (Box 14)
    - English Puritanism, undated (Box 14)
    - English Reformation, undated (Box 14)
    - Enlightened Despotism, undated (Box 14)
    - Enlightenment, undated (Box 14)
    - Expansion of Europe (England), undated (Box 14)
    - Expansion of Europe (Spain), undated (Box 14)
    - Faculty Annual Report (Leo F. Solt) (Box 14)
      - 1975-1981 (Box 14)
      - 1987-1988 (Box 14)
    - Faculty Fellowship Program, 1976 (Box 14)
    - Faculty Summary Report, 1990-1991 (Box 14)
    - Fascist Italy, undated (Box 14)
    - Feudalism, undated (Box 14)
    - First Civilizations, undated (Box 14)
    - Foreign Policy (Mary Stuart and Spain), 1991 (Box 14)
    - France 987-1461, undated (Box 14)
    - France Between the Wars, undated (Box 14)
    - France's Second Empire and Third Republic, undated (Box 14)
    - Free Speech in Parliament, 1952-1953 (Box 14)
    - General Election of 1945, undated (Box 14)
    - General Election of 1945, undated (Box 14)
    - German Conquest of the Roman Empire, undated (Box 14)
    - Gladstone and Ireland, undated (Box 14)
    - Glorious Revolution, undated (Box 14)
    - Golden Age of Shakespeare, undated (Box 14)
    - Graduate Education clippings, 1984 (Box 14)
    - Grants (Box 14)
      - General, 1960-1961 (Box 14)
      - National Endowment Grant, 1967 (Box 14)
      - National Endowment for Humanities, 1970 (Box 14)
    - Great Agricultural Depression, undated (Box 14)
    - Great Reform Bill of 1832, undated (Box 14)
    - Greek Thought and Culture, undated (Box 14)
    - Henry II's Judicial Reforms, 1991 (Box 14)
    - Henry VII, 1977 (Box 14)
    - Henry VII, undated (Box 14)
    - Historians Film Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 14)
    - Historiography, 1991 (Box 14)
    - History Ph.D. Exam Questions (Box 14)
      - 1967-1980 (Box 14)
      - 1990 (Box 14)
    - Hitler and the Nazis, undated (Box 14)
    - Hobbes and Locke, undated (Box 14)
    - Holy Roman Empire 911-1493, undated (Box 14)
    - House of Lords Crisis 1909-1911, undated (Box 14)
    - John Howe, undated (Box 14)
    - Humanism (Box 14)
      - 1972 (Box 14)
      - Undated (Box 14)
    - Humanities, 1974 (Box 14)
    - Humanities, Arts, Social Sciences, Law and Education (HASSLE), 1964-1969 (Box 14)
    - Imperialism, undated (Box 14)
    - Imperialist Russia, undated (Box 14)
    - Industrial Revolution, undated; (2 folders) (Box 14)
    - "Infernal Saints", 1989 (Box 14)
    - Intellectual Revolution, undated (Box 14)
    - Interpretations of Imperialism, undated (Box 14)
    - Interpretations of the Revolution, undated (Box 14)
    - Islam, undated (Box 14)
    - I.U. Press, 1957-1965 (Box 14)
    - James II, undated (Box 14)
    - Jenkins Ear, undated (Box 14)
    - George Karo - clippings, undated (Box 14)
    - King Arthur, undated (Box 14)
    - King's Great Matter, undated (Box 14)
    - Kirkwood Hall and the Old Crescent IU Campus, 1995 (Box 14)
    - Knefelkamp, Lee/ J. Cornfeld materials, 1976-1978 (Box 14)
    - Labor in Transition, undated (Box 14)
    - Last Years of Henry VIII, undated (Box 14)
    - Levellers and Diggers, undated (Box 14)
    - Liberal Reforms, undated (Box 14)
    - Liberalism (English and French), undated (Box 14)
    - Library Search Committee, 1971 (Box 14)
    - Libraries, 1963 (Box 14)
    - Life Magazine Articles, 1947 (Box 14)
    - Little Princes, undated (Box 14)
    - Locke and Hobbes, undated (Box 14)
    - Long Parliament, undated (Box 14)
    - Louis XIV, undated (Box 14)
    - Macaulay and the Whig Interpretation of History, undated (Box 14)
    - Machiavelli, undated (Box 14)
    - Magna Charta, undated (Box 14)
    - Man's Fate, undated (Box 14)
    - Map Lesson, undated (Box 14)
    - Marxian Socialism, undated (Box 14)
    - Mary, Queen of Scots, undated (Box 14)
    - Mary Tudor, undated (Box 14)
    - Master of Arts in Teaching (MAT) advising, 1977; undated (Box 14)
    - Matisse, undated (Box 14)
    - Medieval Art, undated (Box 14)
    - Medieval Castles, undated (Box 14)
    - Medieval Learning, undated (Box 14)
    - Midwest Conference on British Studies (Box 14)
      - 1957-1974 (Box 14)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 14)
      - 1988 (Box 14)
    - Milton and Calvin, undated (Box 14)
    - Miscellaneous clippings, 1944-1978; undated; (2 folders) (Box 15)
    - Napoleon and Europe, undated (Box 15)
    - New Liberalism, undated (Box 15)
    - Norman Conquest, undated (Box 15)
    - Northern Renaissance, undated (Box 15)
    - Organization of American Historians (OAH), Executive Secretary, 1971 (Box 15)
    - Organization of Christianity, undated (Box 15)
    - Origins of World War I, undated (Box 15)
    - Ottoman Empire, undated (Box 15)
    - Parliament in the Thirteenth Century (Edward I), 1989 (Box 15)
    - Personal Government, undated (Box 15)
    - Petition of Right, undated (Box 15)
    - Philosophic Radicals (Bentham), undated (Box 15)
    - Philosophy of Social Science, undated (Box 15)
    - Pleasant Hill Colloquium at Shakertown, 1973 (Box 15)
    - Price and Burke, undated (Box 15)
    - Proceedings in Parliament 1625, undated (Box 15)
    - Punch Coronation Number, 1953 (Box 15)
    - Realism and Anti-Rationalism, undated (Box 15)
    - Reformation Parliament, undated (Box 15)
    - Reign of Henry III (the Gothic Cathedral), undated (Box 15)
    - Reigns of William and Anne, undated (Box 15)
    - Research (Box 15)
      - 1957-1961 (Box 15)
      - 1963-1967 (Box 15)
    - Research Expenses, 1994 (Box 15)
    - Restoration, undated (Box 15)
    - Revolution of 1917, undated (Box 15)
    - Revolutions of 1848, undated (Box 15)
    - Rise of Science, undated (Box 15)
    - Road to War, undated (Box 15)
    - Robin Hood, undated (Box 15)
    - Roman Culture, undated (Box 15)
    - Roman Empire, undated (Box 15)
    - Roman Republic, undated (Box 15)
    - Romanticism and Conservatism, undated (Box 15)
    - Royal Society, undated (Box 15)
    - Sabbatical (Box 15)
      - 1968-1989 (Box 15)
      - 1986-1988 (Box 15)
    - Scheduling, 1977-1978 (Box 15)
    - Scotland Program, 1974-1975; (2 folders) (Box 15)
    - Sermon Manuscript – "Part of a Sermon preached by Mr. Suit at his church the 9th of April," 1643 (Box 15)
      General
      (original and photocopy)
    - Stonehenge, undated (Box 15)
    - Struggle with Rome (Becket), undated (Box 15)
    - Stuart England, undated (Box 15)
    - Study of English History, undated (Box 15)
    - Sutton Hoo: the Coming of the English and Christianity, 1970 (Box 15)
    - Teaching Certificate, 1962-1965 (Box 15)
    - Thirty Years War/Decline of Spain, undated (Box 15)
    - Trade and the Towns, undated (Box 15)
    - Trail of Sir Roger Casement, undated (Box 15)
    - Treaty of Versailles, undated (Box 15)
    - Tudor and Stuart (Box 15)
      - Architecture, 1977 (Box 15)
      - Bibliography, undated (Box 15)
    - Unification of Germany, undated (Box 15)
    - Unification of Italy, undated (Box 15)
    - United Nations, undated (Box 15)
    - University Division Counseling, 1971-1972 (Box 15)
    - Unlabeled audio tape, undated (Box 15)
    - Vertical Files, Bureau of Public Discussion, 1971-1972 (Box 15)
    - Vikings and Anglo-Saxon England, undated (Box 15)
    - Wayne State Trip, Review of History Department, 1985 (Box 15)
    - Weimar Republic, undated (Box 15)
    - Wesleyanism, undated (Box 15)
    - Western Powers (France and Great Britain), undated (Box 15)
    - William Pitt, undated (Box 15)
    - William's Claim to the English Throne, undated (Box 15)
    - World War I, undated (Box 15)
    - World War II, undated (Box 15)
    - World War II, undated (Box 15)
    - World War II, undated (Box 15)
    - Restricted Materials (Box 15-17)